https://www.horizenhydroponics.com/privacy-policy/

Shop Products By Brand Hydroponics Hydroponic Systems Buckets, Trays & Reservoirs Water & Air Pumps Air Stones & Tubing Hydroponic Parts & Tubing Water Filters & Chillers Net Pots & Neoprenes Grow Lights LED Grow Lights HID Ballasts CMH Grow Lights Bulbs Single-Ended HID Reflectors & Fixtures Double-Ended HID Light Meters Fluorescent Timers & Lighting Control Complete Lighting Kits Stands & Movers Components & Cords Plant Nutrients Nutrient Bundles Organic Soil Amendments Bacteria & Fungi Compost & Tea Foliar Sprays Base Nutrients Additives Propagation & Cloning Plantation Temptation Cloning Gels & Solutions Hydroponic Cloning Systems Propagation Supplies Heat Mats Pest & Disease Control Insect & Pest Control Mildew & Disease Control Containers & Media Coco Hydro Stones Rockwool Potting Soil Soilless Mix Containers Saucers pH/ppm Meters & Solutions Meters & Testers Replacement Probes pH Adjustment Solutions Calibration Solutions Maintenance & Cleaning Accessories Grow Tents Shop All Grow Tents Parts & Accessories Environment & Controls Reflective Materials Ducting, Tapes & Clamps Air Conditioning Dehumidifiers & Humidifiers Fans & Blowers CO2 Enrichment Air Purification Environmental Controllers Gardening Supplies Accessories Measuring & Watering Plant Support Garden Hygiene & Safety Scissors & Pruners Sprayers & Wands Electrical Gloves Harvest Curing & Storage Trimming Machines Extraction & Processing Accessories Clearance Items Special OffersSAVE! Good Deals Limited Time Offers Free Shipping Get Offer Emails! Store Locations Grand Rapids, MI Byron Center, MI Kalamazoo, MI Lansing, MI Events Resources Learning Center About Us
Compare Products
My Account
My Wish List
Create an Account
Login
Contact Us
7720 Clyde Park Ave SWByron Center, MI 49315
(616) 791-1664
Our Store Locations
Grand Rapids, MI
Byron Center, MI (Growers Outlet)
Kalamazoo, MI
Lansing, MI
Privacy Policy
Effective date: September 05, 2018
Horizen Hydroponics ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://www.horizenhydroponics.com website (the
"Service").
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use
our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of
information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this
Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from
https://www.horizenhydroponics.com
Information Collection And Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to
you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can
be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is
not limited to:
Email address
First name and last name
Phone number
Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include
information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version,
the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique
device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain
information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to
your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and
scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you
do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various
settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
Horizen Hydroponics uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain the Service
To notify you about changes to our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
To provide customer care and support
To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
To monitor the usage of the Service
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside
of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ
than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer
the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to
that transfer.
Horizen Hydroponics will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in
accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or
a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal
information.
Disclosure Of Data
Legal Requirements
Horizen Hydroponics may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary
to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of Horizen Hydroponics
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security Of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or
method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect
your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide
the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is
used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated
not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic.
Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with
other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its
own advertising network.
You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing
the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js,
analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web
page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you
will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site
you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third
party sites or services.
Children's Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a
parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us.
If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent,
we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy
Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective
and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are
effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By email: weborder@hhydro.com
By visiting this page on our website: https://www.horizenhydroponics.com/contact-us
By phone number: 866.791.1664
By mail: 7720 Clyde Park Ave SW, Byron Center, MI 49315
Horizen Hydroponics strives to offer the most advanced products and services for year round gardening. Be it indoors or outside, Horizen Hydroponics has the product that will make your garden successful!
Information
About Us
Learning Center
Employment
Brands
Covid-19 Preparedness Plan
Customer Service
FREE Shipping
